I remember going to the barbershop when I was little with my dad that I can't talk about.
And they would have these pictures and these numbers and you would order a number haircut.
Yes.
And so there were no names.
It was just the number.
Yes.
So I think, one, if we want to kind of prop up Travis for this phenomenal hair moment,
well, we might need to consider just adding him to one of those charts and giving him a number.
I want to get the number seven and it's Travis Kelsey.
That's true inclusion if we make the haircut a number.
But when we single him out and give him a name, you know, I mean, how many times have you seen
those Black men on the S curl boxes?
You don't know their names.
No, it could be Latrevious.
It could be Latrevious.
It could be Levant.
Yeah, we should find them and give them their flowers this month.